

Portfolio: mrdoker1.github.io/portfolio

Email: <u>fixrapdok@gmail.com</u>

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/kubic/

SUMMARY

I am a (UX/UI) User Experience & Interface Designer and Developer with a technical background and user-centred design thinking, working with E-commerce and SaaS-oriented projects.

My responsibility is to make products clear and helpful to people and make the team's development process smooth and transparent. I enjoy teamwork and am always happy to share knowledge.

SKILLS

- Responsive Web Design, UX, UI Design;
- Mobile Design (IOS, Android);
- Motion Design;
- Vector Illustration, Icons;
- CJM, Sketching, Wireframing, UML Diagrams;
- UX Audit, Competitor Analysis, Usability, AB Testing;
- User-Centered Design, Jobs-To-Be-Done methodology;
- Agile, Scrum/Kanban.

TOOLS

- Adobe Creative Suite (AI, PS, AE);
- Figma, Sketch, XD;
- Protopie, After Effects, Principle;
- Miro,Figjam;
- Axure RP, Invision, Marvel;
- JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Git;
- Tilda, Readymag, other page builders;
- YouTrack, Jira, Trello.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

<u>User Experience: Principles and Processes</u>

RS School Javascript/Front-End 2022Q1

Agile with Atlassian Jira

JavaScript: Basics and Functions

HTML and CSS Fundamentals

Mad Rabbit Illustration Course

PUBLICATIONS

How to Create Landing Pages in Magento?

What are the Latest Web Design Trends 2020?

Other Articles

EXPERIENCE

Oxagile / User Experience Designer

JUL 2022 - PRESENT

As a product designer in internal project have been working on tool which make value for different managing roles and helps Oxagile supervise processes.

Andersen Lab / UI/UX designer

APR 2021 - PRESENT

Creating Web/Mobile Applications, CRM systems Creating UX artifacts such as CJM, User Flows, User Stories, etc.;

Creating sitemap and information architecture;

Producing qualitative and quantitative research and usability testing, social media graphics and digital marketing campaigns;

Cross-platform design experience;

Work in collaboration with key project team members, including tech leads,

Strategy, PMs, and creative leads;

Experience working in an Agile development process.

BelVG / UI/UX designer (E-commerce based)

JAN 2019 - APR 2021

Design stores based on Magento/Presta/WooCommerce/Shopify/osCommerce;

UX Audit, Research;

Wireframing, interaction prototypes design;

Building complex interfaces, UI design;

BelVG Design System, UI Library, Custom Blocks Library;

Internal projects, website, style guides, marketing materials.

Manao / Web Designer

MAR 2017 – JAN 2019

Designing information architecture and creating interactive prototypes;

Website design, applications design, landing pages;

Graphic design;

Illustration/icons and matte painting.

Freelance Local, Upwork

MAY 2016 – MAR 2017

Upwork freelancer - UI Design, Web Design, Marketing, local Smile Coffee - Print, Web Dev, Brand Identity.

EDUCATION

PSU

Faculty of information technologies

SEP 2013 – AUG 2017

A bachelor's degree, Information Technology Software.